[
  {
    "question": "In Pokemon Generation 1, whom does Gary choose if you take Bulbasaur?",
    "answerOne": "Pikachu",
    "answerTwo": "Eevee",
    "answerThree": "Charmander",
    "answerFour": "Squirtle",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Low kick is super effective against which Pokemon?",
    "answerOne": "Lapras",
    "answerTwo": "Arcanine",
    "answerThree": "Pidgeotto",
    "answerFour": "Clefairy",
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Professor's name in Generation 1?",
    "answerOne": "Professor Elm",
    "answerTwo": "Professor Birch",
    "answerThree": "Professor Oak",
    "answerFour": "Professor Pine",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Pokemon Yellow, at which level does Pikachu learn slam?",
    "answerOne": "19",
    "answerTwo": "20",
    "answerThree": "21",
    "answerFour": "22",
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the original Pokemon series, Gyrados is which two types?",
    "answerOne": "Water Dragon",
    "answerTwo": "Flying Dragon",
    "answerThree": "Water Flying",
    "answerFour": "Dragon Electric",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the original Pokemon series, Normal type moves are super effective against which type(s)?",
    "answerOne": "Ghost",
    "answerTwo": "Fighting",
    "answerThree": "Both of the above",
    "answerFour": "None of the above",
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the original Pokemon, what is the name of the item needed to engage with Ghost type pokemon?",
    "answerOne": "Silph Scope ",
    "answerTwo": "Cursed Trinket",
    "answerThree": "Lavender Amulet",
    "answerFour": "Pokeflute",
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which pokemon can be caught in both the Safari Zone, as well as Cerulean Cave?",
    "answerOne": "Kangaskhan",
    "answerTwo": "Chancey",
    "answerThree": "Dragonair",
    "answerFour": "Golem",
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Missingo located?",
    "answerOne": "Viridian City",
    "answerTwo": "Mt. Moon",
    "answerThree": "Cinnibar Island",
    "answerFour": "Rocket Hideout",
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Pokemon do I prefer?",
    "answerOne": "Dragonite",
    "answerTwo": "Machamp",
    "answerThree": "Gengar",
    "answerFour": "Alakazam",
    "correct": "1"
  }
]
